<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Noble Ackerson</title>
    <link>https://nobles.page/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Noble Ackerson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 23:46:41 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nobles.page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Inputs Outputs Outcomes of Product Strategy</title>
      <link>https://nobles.page/blog/the-inputs-outputs-outcomes-of-product-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 23:46:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nobles.page/blog/the-inputs-outputs-outcomes-of-product-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted on Medium
In coaching a few startups I noticed that if your product’s inputs are garbage, the resulting outcomes are garbage, even if the outputs are polished. In this article, I’ll lay out a case for the path to a successful product:  inputs, stewarded by an awesome research team; outputs, governed by a disciplined Agile team; and outcomes, lead by a mature product team  No, it’s not about outcomes over outputs dear product managers, it’s all three.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AR, the Future of our History</title>
      <link>https://nobles.page/blog/ar-future-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 12:18:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nobles.page/blog/ar-future-history/</guid>
      <description>AR, the Future of our History Spatial computing and the “AR cloud” is the future of humanity’s history. I’ll let you know why with a quick story.
My lineage and family history is a tangled web of intrigue, fascination, and wonder. I’ve got roots going back to Ashanti Royalty, yet when I try to tap my family diaspora to share stories of our history, there are only fragments. This is unfortunate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Augmented Reality&#39;s 6th Sense</title>
      <link>https://nobles.page/blog/augmented-reality-6th-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 09:16:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nobles.page/blog/augmented-reality-6th-sense/</guid>
      <description>This updated article now lives on Medium &amp;ldquo;Does AR give us a sixth sense?&amp;rdquo; - https://link.medium.com/upEkfPnRST
Does AR give us a 6th sense? Augmented Reality (AR) is the mixture of the real world and virtual worlds so that one understands the other. The medium affords a deeper connection with the real world giving context without breaking its laws. What makes AR a powerful medium is that it even supersedes our visual senses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking</title>
      <link>https://nobles.page/speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nobles.page/speaking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://nobles.page/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nobles.page/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
